Please cross
the bridge and turn left,
and continue to follow
the road for 42 miles.
Please turn right
and continue for six miles.
Please turn right. You have
reached your destination.
All right. How you doing?
I'm Edmond Murray.
Hi. Can I see your ID, please?
Of course.
Here you go.
Mr. Murray's just arrived.
Copy that.
Good morning. My name's Officer Birch.
How you doing?
I'm the initial investigating officer.
Uh-huh.
Ms. Richmond is waiting for you
over by the water.
I'm Ethan's dad.
I know that, Mr. Murray.
I'm afraid that I cannot
comment any further on the case.
Inspector Roy will be
down here later on.
He'll be able to fill
you in on any questions.
Okay. Ms. Richmond is
just down by the water,
if you follow the path over to the right.
Okay. Thank you.
Joan!
Fuck. Joan!
What are they doing out there?
They're looking for him.
They think he's in the water?
I don't know.
What the fuck happened?
That's where he was sleeping.
You all right?
I can't go back there.
Can I go in there?
No, sorry.
Fuck.
I've rented this place.
I'm going to stay here.
Okay, I'll stay somewhere near.
Good.
Would you be able
to do something for me?
Mm-hmm.
I need you to go back
to the house.
Ethan drew me a picture
the day before he left and...
I can't stop thinking about it.
Thanks.
Do we know anything about the
people that run that camp?
No, they said
they've questioned everyone.
Did you meet them?
Before you sent him?
Yeah, I mean...
They seemed really lovely.
The woman was really lovely.
I don't... Uh-huh.
I... I'm sure they were fine.
I'm sure they were fine.
I never would have sent him there if I
thought that there was anything wrong. Ever!
I know, I know.
You're a good mum.
I know.
Hi.
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- It was fine.
- What did they want to know?
Well, they just had
some questions.
What sort of stuff?
My relationship with Ethan.
Why?
No. Are you on your way back?
Can you come back?
Okay, all right.
- Bye. I love you.
- Love you. Bye.
Is that your man?
Yeah.
Was it his idea
to send him to the camp?
Oh, fucking hell.
Yeah, sure, it was his idea.
He's my son. Okay?
It was my choice.
I wish he hadn't gone.
So do I. I didn't want him to
go in the first place, but...
kids his age,
they're doing stuff like that.
And Ethan's not... He's...
He's different, and he...
he didn't want to go.
And I knew he didn't want to go.
He seemed okay, before he went?
I just...
I just needed a...
I'm sorry.
Was it...
He's been having a hard time.
Okay?
All right?
Get them ready to go.
Inspector, this is Eddy,
Ethan's dad.
All right, Mr. Murray.
I'm Inspector Roy.
Inspector.
I'm running the investigation
with my team here.
Mr. Murray, I'd like you to come into my
office this afternoon at 3:00, please.
Of course, 3:00.
The details are on the card.
And my personal mobile number is
on the back, should you need it.
Miss, are you sure
you want to take part in this?
Yeah.
Yesterday, you seemed... No.
You sure? I'm here. I can take over.
No, I want to do it.
Very good.
If you'll just listen
to the instructions
and then I'll tell you
where to stand.
Okay. Thank you.
Attention, please, everyone!
This morning, we're going
to search this entire slope.
I want you to move
through the bracken together.
You keep two meters apart.
If you find anything,
you raise your hand
and you shout, "Here!"
It's very important
that you touch nothing.
Understood?
All right.
Thank you all for coming.
Take your positions, please.
Where do you want us? You can stand
here, at the end of this line.
Thank you.
Two meters, two meters.
Kennis!
Let's go!
Ethan! Ethan!
Ethan!
- Who's she?
- Inspector Roy can tell you.
Please, come with me.
How you doing?
Mr. Murray. Please.
Is there any news?
Nothing, as yet.
How are you coping?
I've... I've known
better days, you know?
Allow me to tell you
where we are.
The alert plan
has been triggered
since yesterday morning. Good.
We continue to interview everybody who
has come into contact with your son.
Now, the supervising
staff at the camp,
they tell me that they would do regular
checks of the tents and the pods,
to make sure that the children
were asleep and all was well.
The last check took place
at 1:00 in the morning.
And he was in there?
He was in there. At that
point, everything was fine.
When I looked at his cabin,
I could see his clothes were still
in there, his bag was still in there.
His little snacks
were still in there.
Now, Mr. Murray,
I have to tell you that we're
investigating every hypothesis,
including kidnapping.
Now, allow me to ask you
a number of questions.
You may find some of these questions
unsettling, intimate. May I?
No, don't worry. You can
ask me whatever you want.
First of all, I understand that
you've been traveling a great deal.
You've been in Libya, Saudi Arabia, Iraq.
Why is that?
My work's international.
I've been working abroad
for the last ten years,
um, give or take.
I work in the oil fields,
and I go wherever they send me.
Would you say your business,
your work was dangerous?
The work, in itself,
is not dangerous.
You can sometimes be in places
where you are in danger.
And I am constantly aware,
when I'm in certain places,
that I need to watch my back.
Have any of these things
affected you, Mr. Murray?
Ah...
A subordinate of mine
was taken hostage.
We went through a whole fiasco
trying to get him back.
It was a fucking mess. And we
ended up paying the hostage ransom.
Sir...
Oh, come on. If you've got something
to say, you can say it in English.
I'd like to ask you
for your mobile phone.
We need it for the purposes of the
investigation, to retrieve the contacts.
It's procedure. I'm not
supposed to give my phone out.
I'm sure you can appreciate the
importance of this, at this point in time.
I completely can.
The nature of my work means
there's sensitive material on here.
You just need my contacts? Yes.
Thank you.
It would be fair to say that most
of the countries where you work
would be unsuitable to take a
child to, yes? Most of them, yes.
The hours that I work, and the
far-flung places I end up in,
even if they aren't insecure,
aren't suitable for taking a child.
I can't take him all over the world.
He's got to be in school.
He's got to have his friends,
got to have some stability.
He's got to have a house, a family.
And I can't offer him that.
When did you last see your son?
I saw him at Christmas time.
I saw him...
I saw him on Skype
at Christmas time.
He seemed fine.
Do you have a good relationship
with your ex-wife?
It's not... It's not bad.
It's not her fault we split up.
Is there any antagonism?
From me, none.
Do you have any contact
with her new partner?
I've seen him on Skype
a few times. He seems fine.
Have you security checked him?
Because isn't it well known
that nine times out of ten,
it's someone you know,
someone in your family?
This is the case, which is why it's
part of our primary investigation.
And you? Is there someone new
in your life?
Yes.
Yes, I have a partner.
I've been seeing her
for five years.
Two years ago, your wife told
you that your son was unwell.
I came back and we went
away together for a month.
We had a cracking time.
We went all over North America.
And...
And then I went back to work.
Do you have reason to believe
that it's because of what I do
that Ethan has been taken?
I have reason to believe
that somebody made a decision
to choose your son
and not the other child.
That's why I'm asking you these
questions, Mr. Murray. Why Ethan?
Why him? Why not the other boy?
Unfortunately, all you can do
at this point in time is wait.
Wait for us to contact you.
- How you doing?
- Edmond.
Nice to see you.
Come in.
All right. Thank you.
Joan? Where's Joan?
Ah...
She... She's resting. Sit down.
You want a whiskey?
Aye. Sure, thank you.
Brutal weather outside, eh?
Uh-huh. Apparently,
it's going to be...
It's going to be
an early winter, apparently.
I mean, that's what, you know,
the locals are saying.
All the old people.
But no one fucking believes them
anymore, do they?
They just believe the...
the fucking Internet.
Slainte.
Joan's just...
She really broke down tonight.
You know, I just think it
really fucking...
really hit her.
I know. Fair enough.
So I've just given her a little
something to help her sleep.
So hopefully
she'll get a full night,
so I'm not gonna...
What did you give her?
Fuck. I don't know
the name of it. Um...
I... I struggle
with sleep occasionally
and I got a prescription
fucking ages ago but...
How long has she been
asleep for, with that?
Um...
About an hour and a half ago,
something like that.
But I don't think... I don't think
I should wake her up, really.
She needs the rest.
Nothing to worry about.
Okay.
Yeah.
It's not a regular thing.
In the circumstances... All right, man.
All right. Yep.
So what are you...
What's going to happen with your work?
What are you going to do?
Ah, work can wait.
It's easy for me, really, 'cause I
work for myself. I set up a business.
I've got this
construction company and...
I mean, it's, you know, small but
I've had it for about 15 years.
I started in my early 20s.
Based here?
International?
No. No, I'm not like you. No.
No, I... I want to stay here.
Local, really.
It's small, you know.
I started it myself.
It was a grind, believe me.
But now I've recruited
enough people
that it just kind of
runs itself, which is great.
So I can now essentially just be
here, be there for Joan and...
Nothing more important
than that, eh?
She's fucking amazing, man.
Have you heard anything?
Has anybody called or...
Today?
Uh-huh.
What about?
The searches? No, no.
To be honest with you, my focus
is really on her, you know.
I'm just focusing on her.
No. I'm actually just going to
switch my phone off for a bit.
Is that a good idea?
Well, you're here.
You've got your phone on, no?
I just wanted
to have a conversation...
Yeah. No, no.
I just don't
want to be disturbed.
So where are you going to stay?
Joan said you
don't really have anywhere
around here anymore.
Don't worry about me, Frank. I'll be fine.
I'll find something.
Why don't you stay at Joan's? I mean, it's
technically your... your place, as well.
Aye. Well, if you're not
going to be there...
Listen, I understand that you
and Joan might need some space.
No, look, it's... Time together.
I can... I can escape.
My parents... I inherited this little
shack in the middle of fucking nowhere.
I can go and, you know,
get out of the way.
I'm selling it, actually.
Because, following in your footsteps,
I found this unbelievable bit of land,
and now we're going to
build a house,
and it's just so beautiful.
Joan loves it.
The light is amazing.
Actually, can I...
Can I show you something?
Here, come into the kitchen.
Come on.
So these got delivered today, actually.
I was just looking over them.
So, I've been working with this architect.
He works in my company.
So he's designing it with me,
and Joan also.
So this is the outside of the house.
The sea is here.
And we've got all the light here.
It's beautiful. Glass here.
Actually, I think
I want a bit more.
But then this is the top floor.
We've got our bedroom here.
Lots of light for Joan.
It's going to be unbelievable.
And then down here is the basement. Just
don't really know what to do with it.
Maybe...
Maybe a games room or...
Be careful. What do you think?
Are you actually
fucking kidding me?
Um...
Where's Ethan's room?
Okay...
Are you putting him
in the basement?
No, we're not putting him
in the basement.
I can see that you're
angry and upset... Joan!
Hey, hey, hey! She's asleep. No.
She's asleep.
I need to talk to her.
Hey.
Why? She's asleep.
'Cause my fucking son's missing.
Yeah, I'm aware of that. I'm
aware that your son's missing.
He's also my son.
I love him very much.
Don't. Fucking don't.
Don't what?
Don't tell me he's your son, as well.
Well, let's be honest.
He's been... He's been more my son than
he has yours the last year, hasn't he?
You're a very fucking weird man!
What have you done with my son?
I've done nothing with your son. What
the fuck have you done with my son?
I love your son! What
the fuck have you done?
Inspector Roy,
you need to come over here.
I'm at Joan's
rented accommodation.
I'm here with her partner,
Frank. He's unconscious.
He's been high as a kite.
He's given her drugs.
And he knows something.
He fucking knows something.
Please call me back at this
number as soon as you can.
- Get the fuck off!
- Get in the van! Get in the van!
Please, you're making a mistake!
You're making a big mistake!
Hey, there's a picture in the bag.
Just give it to Joan!
Just get in the van!
You're making a mistake!
What? Section 1 of the
Criminal Justice Act...
You don't understand.
The man has taken my son.
Or he's done something to my son, or he
fucking knows something about my son.
You've gotta go back there!
You take me to fucking jail,
and you're taking him
to the hospital?
Do you understand?
You're having a fucking laugh!
Informed of your arrest and
you'll have access to a solicitor.
These rights...
Fuck!
Will be explained to you further
once we arrive at the police station.
I suggest you make yourself
comfortable, Mr. Murray.
I don't care
how fucking badly he is hurt.
The minute he wakes up, you need to
ask him what he's done with my son.
You're not going
to say anything?
Nothing?
My son's missing!
Fuck.
That's my wallet.
That's...
They're actually Joan's keys.
That's Frank's phone.
That's my phone.
You want to put that
somewhere else?
Put it in there, please.
That could be evidence.
Make yourself at home.
All right.
Obviously, you'll be held
in custody until the morning.
I'll come back then and we'll
see what's to happen to you.
I'm really sorry
about everything that happened.
But have you spoken to him yet?
I have to impress upon you,
Mr. Murray,
you're wasting our time now.
Every hour is critical,
and you're wasting our time.
There's something
not right about that guy.
The day after my wee boy's
gone missing,
he's showing me
blueprints of some house
that he wants to move into
with my wife... my... my ex-wife.
And he doesn't have a room
in that house for my son.
Either he knows something or
he's criminally a fucking prick.
Please, Joan's taking Valium
and going to sleep.
I have known that woman.
She's a good mother
and she would not take anything
that would stop her
answering that phone.
She would be up checking
that phone every 15 minutes.
So I am really sorry. I apologize.
I'm not going to talk anymore.
But please,
just treat him seriously.
You're not stable right now.
I'm telling you straight.
You're in no position to tell me
how to conduct this investigation.
I'll see you.
It's my wee boy...
Mr. Gilchrist
is still in hospital.
He has two fractured ribs.
He has a dislocated hip.
Nonetheless, he's decided not
to press charges against you.
Were you able to talk to him?
I've communicated with him.
I have taken a similar position.
I'm not going to take
this any further, Mr. Murray.
One of my colleagues
has retrieved your car.
It's at the station here.
You're letting me go?
You're no longer in custody.
You don't think it's weird that
he's not going to press charges?
Mr. Murray, I'll explain
something very significant to you,
to help you clear
your mind of all of this.
One month ago, your wife
suffered a miscarriage.
What?
Yes.
I'm telling you this, so that
you can understand the situation,
the predicament of both Ms.
Richmond and Frank Gilchrist.
Now, this was a very difficult
thing for her to deal with.
In fact, this is the reason that she
decided to send your son to the camp.
So that she could get some calm,
some peace, to deal with this.
It was nothing to do
with Mr. Gilchrist.
Is she all right?
In these circumstances, no.
And I understand that this is a
very difficult period for you.
I'd like to offer you
psychological support.
You need to go home.
You need to clear your head
of this,
to allow us to go
on with the investigation.
No, I'm fine.
I won't be any more problem
to you, I promise.
Thank you. Thank you
for your patience.
Hi, this is Leah. Leave me a message.
Thank you.
Leah, it's Edmond. Um...
I'm here. I'm sorry I've
not checked in earlier.
I got in a bit of trouble
with the police last night.
I'm fine. I'm absolutely fine.
And we haven't heard
anything about...
what's happened to Ethan yet.
Could you tell the company I'm
really sorry I haven't checked in?
Can you do that for me? Tell them
I'm okay and I'll be in touch soon.
Um...
I love you.
If you get this call,
just please call me back, okay?
Joan! Joan?
Joan.
You okay?
Have they found him?
No. Not yet.
Joan.
I'm really sorry
for what happened to you.
What do you mean?
About your wee baby.
I'm very sorry.
Who told you that?
Inspector Roy.
He was trying to...
Well, he's got no fucking right
to tell you that.
I know you guys were going through a
very difficult time, even before this.
Fuck off.
Was it hard for Ethan?
'Cause he said that you...
I...
You needed peace and...
I mean, this is bad
enough, as it is.
I don't know what
you're trying to do to me.
I'm not trying to do anything.
He didn't...
He didn't want me
to have a baby.
Ethan?
No, of course he didn't.
Does that make you happy?
That he hated it?
No.
'Cause he fucking hated
the idea.
He hated that
Frank had moved in.
And he hated the fact
that you weren't here anymore.
And the only person he could talk to
about it was me, because you weren't here.
So I had to deal with our son
being upset about something
that I was really happy about.
I'm really sorry about that.
Where were you last night?
I was in the police station.
They just let me out.
They said Frank's not going
to press any charges.
He fucking should.
Did he give you
Valium last night?
Yeah.
I've never known you
to take a pill in your life.
Well, you don't know me anymore.
Okay.
I thought you were going
to say you were sorry.
That's what I thought
you were going to say.
I thought you were going to say
sorry for beating the shit
out of my boyfriend.
You know, he never even
mentioned Ethan.
He's all excited about his blueprints
for his new house that's he's building.
Yeah, we were
really excited about that!
We were really excited about that.
Ethan was excited about that.
And we all talked about it together,
as a family. Me, him and Frank.
We all sat down and we discussed it.
That's what we do. That's my family.
And you'd know that
if you asked about him,
if you asked your son about him.
But you don't, do you?
Because you never fucking call
and you never
fucking do anything.
You sent a present
on his seventh birthday.
He doesn't even get the chance
to talk to his dad.
Have you even thought about
what this all means?
That your son's missing?
All I've been thinking about
this whole time
is that I'm a bad mother,
that I've done something wrong.
Have you even thought for a fucking
second what sort of father you are?
What sort of father
you've been to your son?
I know, I know.
I know I'm a bad dad.
I know I'm never here.
I know he can't rely on me.
But it's not my fault
he's gone missing, darling.
I just...
Hey, hey!
Stop and think for a minute.
Just think of what
we need you to do.
Frank is not...
He's a beautiful, strong,
amazing man who loves your son.
I don't believe that.
Right.
Why do you think
that my phone is being tapped?
Listen. At 2:00 this afternoon,
I got a call from Glasgow.
They asked me
to come off this case.
I said, "Why? Why should I
drop this file? Why?
You must send me a written explanation
why I should drop this file."
And they yell at me,
shout at me. And I hung up.
At 2:17, I get a call,
this time from London.
From Sir Patrick Nelson.
This man, he's higher up than anybody
in the police force in Scotland.
And he tells me this case
will be handled from London.
This time,
I get a chance to say nothing.
He tells me that this is
in everyone's best interests.
And that's it.
At 3:00, I tell my team we're
no longer involved. And I leave.
I didn't have much faith in a kidnapping
related to your work in the oil industry.
I could be wrong.
London must have some
information that I don't have.
But I'll tell you this.
You're on your own. Basically,
you're on your own, Mr. Murray.
I can't stay.
Don't use your phone.
Thank you.
Come on, darling. Pick up.
- Hello?
- Leah?
- Can you hear me?
- What's this number?
What's this number
you're phoning on?
It's not my phone.
Listen to me,
listen to me, listen to me.
No, you listen to me. Do you have
any idea what's been going on here?
Do you know the cops came into the office?
They turned the whole place upside down.
They've got the computers. They've got the
hard drives. They've got everything, Edmond.
- Do you understand what this means?
- What?
They've got all the files. I
mean, they've got the Iraq files.
I mean, Jesus!
Has anybody mentioned my name?
Has anybody been looking for me?
Listen to me.
Listen to me, Edmond, okay?
I've gotta tell you this. Don't
call me again. Do you understand?
- Leah...
- Do you understand? I'm sorry.
Can I take it off?
Yeah, sure.
- Oh, my God!
- Joan.
That is not what
I was expecting at all.
What do you think?
It's amazing, eh?
- It's amazing.
- I know! We can build a house along here.
I was thinking this is where,
you know, if you wanted to...
we could, you know,
start a family.
Yeah.
Yeah! I want to, yeah.
- Well, I love you very much.
- -I love you.
You clever, clever man.
Ready? Make a wish!
Three, two, one! Come on!
One more, one more, one more.
Come on, come on, come on!
Come on, come on!
Don't leave me hanging!
Yay!
Do you like it?
Okay, okay.
Let's open the big one now.
This is the one.
This is from Daddy,
who wishes he could be here,
but he can't be here today.
This is from Dad.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, my goodness.
What's that?
It's a helicopter.
Isn't that amazing? Yeah?
Ethan, how do you like
your present from your dad?
Yeah? Good present? All right!
You're doing really good.
You're a good mum.
You are a good mother.
A rocket!
Whoa!
Oh, my God!
You got that?
Ethan! You having fun?
Are you happy?
You having a good birthday?
Look, Ethan! Look! What do you think?
It's pretty cool, eh?
You're going to be hanging out
with that guy.
Hey? Look at that!
Hi, guys! How you doing?
Yeah, sure.
You want to say goodbye
to your pal?
See ya!
Are you all ready
for this, junior astronauts?
- Yeah!
- -That's what I like to hear!
Okay, so, just to let
you know, Mums and Dads,
before you head off,
we've got loads of busy days...
Love you.
You'll be all right, okay?
Just try and enjoy it.
You'll have a great time.
Say bye-bye to them,
Mums and Dads.
I love you, darling.
Bye, Ethan buddy!
Have fun!
Bye, Ethan!
There we go.
The first... The first time
he's slept away from home.
- Bye, darling! Love you!
- Bye, Ethan!
Come on,
give us a wave. Bye, bud!
Go on, Ethan!
Go, go, go!
Come over here.
- Who wants a balloon?
- Me!
They're all tangled up.
They're going to be
well-fed. They're...
Astronomy camp...
Have fun!
Hi, are you okay?
Frank?
Hey, Joan.
It's not Frank. It's me.
- Why are you calling me on Frank's phone?
- I took it off him last night.
The police thought it was mine,
so they gave it back to me.
Please, before you get angry
with me, can you listen to me?
Can I come over? I'll give you...
Why?
I think I've found something.
You're going to be
hanging out with that guy, eh?
Isn't that amazing?
Want to say goodbye to your pal?
I can't watch this.
Why are we watching this?
See ya!
Just have a look at this.
The same car?
Two different places,
two different times,
and the common factor
being our son.
Well, the common factor's
not our son.
The common factor is that he was at a
birthday party with all his friends,
and then he went to adventure
camp with all his friends.
So that's... It's probably
just one of the parents' cars.
That's fine, that's fine. Worst-case
scenario, I'll turn up at his mate's house
and I'll get a sympathetic cup
of tea with some innocent dad.
I think you need
to call your brother.
Oh, fuck...
Call your brother.
He still works in insurance.
He'll be able to get the license plate.
He'll be able to get the home address.
Yeah, illegally.
I still think... I still think we
should call the police. I can't...
I told you before...
I know! I can't...
We are on our own. Darling,
we are all that Ethan's got.
Those were Inspector Roy's
last words to me.
Call your brother. Now.
They might have already moved him.
Fine, fine!
Go, go, go.
Rob, Hi. No, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry it's so early.
Yeah, I know.
No. Nothing yet, no. Um...
Look, I need you to do something
for me, if you can.
I don't know, it looks like a
house or a building or something.
It's in the middle of nowhere.
It's not that far away.
If I take the long road, I can
come around on it from behind.
All right, look, William O'Connor.
Have you ever heard that name?
No. I don't know.
All right, fuck it.
Fuck it. All right,
I'll come with you.
No, no, no, no. No!
You have to let me go.
No, I can't just stay here.
If something happens to me,
he's going to need
one of us. Okay?
Just think before you do anything, okay?
Don't do anything stupid.
Uh-huh.
All right?
And if you're not back by midday,
then I'm calling the police.
That's it! Okay?
That's it, Eddy!
Call Inspector Roy.
All right.
I've got Frank's phone.
Maybe, maybe, maybe, you might see a
shooting star or a comet or something.
Wow! Your mum has done
amazing research into this camp.
I think I just saw
a little smile.
You will reach
your destination in 300 yards.
your destination in 200 yards.
You will reach
your destination in 100 yards.
You have reached
your destination.
Turn around.
It's too dangerous now. I need to wait.
I'll leave in 20, I think.
Okay.
Look at me. Look up.
What the...
Look at me. Look at me.
Do you know who I am?
No.
Do you know why I'm here?
I know who you are.
What are you talking about?
I've got pictures of you.
I got pictures of your car.
My car?
Outside the Lockey Camp.
What?
Outside the climbing center
in Crianlarich
for two weeks following my son.
Do you know who I am?
You're fucking mental, man.
Do you know why I'm here?
You're making
a mistake here, man!
This is fucking nothing...
Tell me what I want to know!
I don't know what you're
fucking talking about, man.
Tell me what I want to know!
What about?
Where's my fucking son?
You've made a mistake, man!
Just fucking untie me
and let me...
Tell me where my fucking son is!
Or I will drive this up through
your mouth, up through your brain,
and outta the top of your fucking head.
Do you understand?
I don't fucking know!
You fuck!
What are you fucking doing, man?
Don't fucking do that, man!
You've made a mistake.
Untie me, let me go, and I'll say
fuck all about this, mate, all right?
Man, what are you fucking doing?
Man, don't fucking do that, man!
I don't fucking know!
Tell me where my wee boy is.
Fucking tell me where my wee boy is.
I don't fucking know.
You going to tell me
where my wee boy is?
I don't fucking know...
What the fuck!
Where's my fucking son?
I don't fucking know, man!
I don't fucking... No, man!
You take my fucking son?
Don't fucking do that!
I'm going to burn your fucking feet off.
No, don't do that!
Tell me right now!
I don't fucking know.
Where the fuck is my son?
I don't know.
Where's my fucking son?
You going to tell me?
Okay, okay, okay!
Tell me where he is.
He... He...
What? Fucking speak!
Dunmore Lodge.
Where?
We take 'em there.
We drop them there and they
come and pick them up later.
Who?
I don't fucking know.
Who? I fucking swear! I swear!
I don't fucking know that,
man! I swear...
I don't fucking touch them, man.
I'm not like them!
I'm not fucking like them.
I'm not like that. I just deliver them.
I drop them off and that's fucking it.
You don't touch them?
Never, man. Never.
Who touches them?
I don't know, man.
I just... I take photos.
Fucking...
I take photos
outside the schools.
And then...
And then they pick them.
I'm sorry, man.
Don't fucking hell, man! No!
He should be here.
Huh?
He should've been here
at least 15 minutes ago!
Call him again, then.
William, where the fuck are you?
You're late!
Come on. Spit it out.
Get in. Get in.
He's still not picking up.
- Shit!
- I don't like this.
There's cops everywhere.
They put roadblocks everywhere.
The whole area's swarming
with cops. Maybe he got nicked.
Forget the girl. Let's take
what we have and get outta here.
They really wanted
the girl, though.
Okay.
We're not staying here.
Let's go.
- Let's go!
- Hurry up!
Fuck.
Fuck it!
Steven! It's fucking flat.
When did that happen?
It must have been done on
the road, when we drove here.
Probably a nail or a screw.
Those can make it deflate slowly.
It takes me five minutes
to put the spare on.
Take the kid back inside.
I'll call you when I'm finished.
Steven?
Steven!
Where the fuck is he?
Where are the fucking keys?
Give me your fucking keys.
Here we go!
Steven!
Inspector Roy, it's Joan Richmond. Can
you call me as soon as you get this?
Steven! Are you there?
Are you there?
Steven!
What the fuck
are you playing at?
Steven!
Where the fuck is he?
Have you seen Steven?
He's not downstairs?
Have you got the car keys?
No, Steven has them.
Where the fuck is he?
Call him!
Shh, shh, shh...
Steven, where the hell are you?
We're looking all over for you.
Listen to me.
That wee boy that you've got is my son.
The police are on their way.
You have to leave the little boy
where he is and just run away.
It's your only shot, pal.
You listen to me, prick.
I'm coming for you.
Stay with the boy.
What if the cops come? Bullshit!
Do what I told you.
Fuck!
Hey, man! Hey, man!
Hey, Ethan!
Ethan, can you wake up, pal?
Can you wake... Can you wake up?
You stay asleep.
Eddy!
Joan!
Shh, shh! Come this way.
Come on, quickly.
You okay?
Yeah.
Fuck!
Is he still following us?
I can't see.
Joan...
Joan!
Eddy?
- Eddy!
Eddy!
It's all right! It's all right! It's me.
You're safe, you're safe.
Oh, geez! The boy...
The boy is all right.
It's all right.
There you go. Just be
real gentle and take it over
to the left, like that.
Oh, you see it bob like that?
- You want a go?
- Yeah, you want a go?
- Yeah, sure.
- You want to try it? Okay.
Here we go.
Right. Here we go, the vital
moment, the transference of power.
Get your fingers on it.
Ready?
Get your fingers on it!
There, you've got it, wee man.
It's all yours.
Well done, Ethan.
Well done, pal.
Is it good?
Don't bring it too close towards you.
I want to keep my hair.
You cheeky thing...
Whoa!
So good, wee man. So good.
I'm going to leave this to you, 'cause
you seem to know what you're doing.
You do!
Kinda.
It's making me scared.
Don't drop it on our heads!
Whoa!
Wow!
You'll be a pilot for the MOD
before you know it.
Mr. Murray!
Hey, pal...
I'm going to need to get going.
Should we land it
and say a proper bye-bye?
Okay, all right.
I love you, pal.
When are you coming back?
Um...
I might be a wee while. Okay.
But I am going to come back.
I'll come back
and be here, okay?
Okay.
See ya, Joan.
See ya.
You okay?
Yeah.
Whoa!
The dismantling of the network
is accelerating, you know.
I believe that there
will be more arrests.
It'll be a big list.
What a shame.
But it could be good for you.
You think?
Yes. The judge will probably
take this into account.
Aye, hopefully.